[{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679094839,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":12011,"timeElapsed":262181},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679104577,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":9731,"timeElapsed":271919},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679115299,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":10717,"timeElapsed":282640},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679119649,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":4346,"timeElapsed":286990},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679129767,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":10116,"timeElapsed":297109},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679150285,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":20514,"timeElapsed":317627},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679204305,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":54020,"timeElapsed":371647},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679212872,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":8566,"timeElapsed":380214},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679216072,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":3199,"timeElapsed":383414},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679277408,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":60235,"timeElapsed":444750},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679279792,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":2382,"timeElapsed":447134},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679284175,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":4383,"timeElapsed":451517},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679286343,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":2166,"timeElapsed":453685},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679290475,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4131,"timeElapsed":457817},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679292942,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":2465,"timeElapsed":460284},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679294776,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":1833,"timeElapsed":462118},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679358229,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":63452,"timeElapsed":525571},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679359946,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":1716,"timeElapsed":527288},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679370680,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":9699,"timeElapsed":538021},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679374529,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3847,"timeElapsed":541871},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679377747,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":3215,"timeElapsed":545089},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679379546,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":1797,"timeElapsed":546887},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679381763,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2217,"timeElapsed":549105},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679389047,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":7282,"timeElapsed":556389},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679395330,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6282,"timeElapsed":562672},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679398865,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3534,"timeElapsed":566206},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679400880,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2014,"timeElapsed":568222},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679415499,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":6680,"timeElapsed":582840},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679417368,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":1865,"timeElapsed":584710},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679419715,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":2346,"timeElapsed":587057},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679421515,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":1799,"timeElapsed":588857},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679425198,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":3682,"timeElapsed":592540},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679430582,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5382,"timeElapsed":597923},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679436716,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":6133,"timeElapsed":604058},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679438866,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":2148,"timeElapsed":606208},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679442516,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":3649,"timeElapsed":609858},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679444849,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":2332,"timeElapsed":612191},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679466250,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":19601,"timeElapsed":633592},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679468300,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2049,"timeElapsed":635642},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679470267,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":1966,"timeElapsed":637609},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679472284,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2016,"timeElapsed":639626},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679477768,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":5483,"timeElapsed":645110},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679480401,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":2632,"timeElapsed":647743},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679482235,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":1832,"timeElapsed":649576},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679486218,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":3982,"timeElapsed":653559},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679487868,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":1648,"timeElapsed":655210},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679535736,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":47068,"timeElapsed":703078},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679537686,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":1949,"timeElapsed":705028},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679540054,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":2366,"timeElapsed":707395},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679541954,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":1899,"timeElapsed":709296},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679544220,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":2266,"timeElapsed":711562},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679546137,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":1916,"timeElapsed":713479},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679549471,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":3332,"timeElapsed":716812},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679555321,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":5850,"timeElapsed":722663},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679558221,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":2898,"timeElapsed":725563},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679572855,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":12416,"timeElapsed":740197},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679574539,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":1684,"timeElapsed":741881},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679576972,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":2431,"timeElapsed":744314},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679578739,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":1765,"timeElapsed":746080},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679581822,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":3082,"timeElapsed":749164},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679583856,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2034,"timeElapsed":751198},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679586689,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":2831,"timeElapsed":754031},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679590073,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":3382,"timeElapsed":757415},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679594639,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":4565,"timeElapsed":761981},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679622607,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":26149,"timeElapsed":789949},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679624357,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":1749,"timeElapsed":791699},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679626291,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":1932,"timeElapsed":793632},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679627741,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":1449,"timeElapsed":795083},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679629791,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":2049,"timeElapsed":797133},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679632959,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3166,"timeElapsed":800301},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679634741,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":1782,"timeElapsed":802083},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679640108,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5366,"timeElapsed":807450},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679684310,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":44202,"timeElapsed":851652},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679686127,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":1816,"timeElapsed":853469},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679695977,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":8683,"timeElapsed":863319},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679699194,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":3216,"timeElapsed":866536},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679703110,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":3916,"timeElapsed":870452},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679705445,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":2333,"timeElapsed":872787},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679709527,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":4082,"timeElapsed":876869},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679711944,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2415,"timeElapsed":879286},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679714761,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2816,"timeElapsed":882103},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679718278,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":3517,"timeElapsed":885620},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679720812,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":2531,"timeElapsed":888154},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679728430,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":6400,"timeElapsed":895772},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679730513,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2082,"timeElapsed":897854},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679734962,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":4447,"timeElapsed":902304},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679736662,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":1699,"timeElapsed":904004},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679742063,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5400,"timeElapsed":909405},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679744546,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":2482,"timeElapsed":911888},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679747062,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2516,"timeElapsed":914404},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679749629,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":2566,"timeElapsed":916971},{"subjectID":"5bjyb5sr9g","prolificID":"66c0df311f98d7c9661669d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b376cf0b1926e118efa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679751630,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":1999,"timeElapsed":918972}]